RG 014, Department of Banking
Connecticut State Library
Department of Banking records
1865-2011
bulk 1918-1963
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Banking Dept
98.25 cubic feet
After a number of Connecticut banks failed during the depression of 1929, in 1935 the General Assembly assigned to the Banking Commissioner the responsibility for liquidating their affairs. These are mainly records from the Liquidation Division. Also included are press releases and Commissioners files.
RG014
1983-002 (except where noted)
Historical Note
The Banking Department originated in an 1836 act of the General Assembly appointing a committee (the Treasurer, the Comptroller, and the Commissioner of the School Fund) to examine the banks of the state. This they did, and in their report recommended the appointment of two Bank Commissioners to continue the work. Their functions were expanded in subsequent years to include examination and supervision of not only state banks and trust companies but also savings and industrial banks, state-chartered credit unions and other financial entities. The Connecticut Bank Commissioners were replaced by the Connecticut Bank Commissioner in 1915. A number of Connecticut banks failed during the depression of 1929, and in 1935 the General Assembly assigned to the Banking Commissioner the responsibility for liquidating their affairs. In 1951, the Bank Commissioner became the head of the Connecticut Banking Department. On January 1, 1979, Connecticut Banking Department was reorganized into the Connecticut Division of Banking, a division of the Department of Business Regulation. Effective July 1, 1980, the Department of Business Regulation was eliminated and the Division of Banking was made the Department of Banking and predominately called itself the Banking Department.
See also the.
Scope and Content
Includes receivership files and records of foreclosures, correspondence concerning closed banks, and administrative files. In addition, the collection contains the records taken over from the banks that were in receivership. Included in the bank records are legal papers, income tax returns, real estate files, correspondence, and bank records of accounts. Also included are incorporation files and special charters, bank returns, press releases, and Commissioners files.
Arrangement
Series 1. Receivership Files, 1918-1971, 92.5 cubic feet
Lawsuits against Banks, circa 1930-1939, 2 cubic feet
General Correspondence, circa 1920-1969, 6 cubic feet
Complete Bank Files, circa 1930-1959, 4 cubic feet
Trust Department, circa 1920-1959, 2 cubic feet
Special Banking Subjects, circa 1940-1959, 7 cubic feet
By-Laws of Savings Banks, circa 1930-1949, 2 cubic feet
Legislation, circa 1940-1971, 12 cubic feet
Pension Plans, circa 1940-1970, 2 cubic feet
Trustees under Mortgage, 1938-1950, 1 cubic foot
Insurance Policies, circa 1940-1949, 2 cubic feet
Closed and Merged Banks, circa 1940-1969, 1 cubic foot
Bank records, circa 1918-1967, 45 cubic feet
Bank Records of Accounts, 1952, .5 cubic feet (29 reels)
Final file, undated, 1.5 inches
Description of property in receivership offered for sale, 1945, 1 inch
Federal tax papers, 1945-1950, 1 inch
Record of foreclosures, 1929-1937, .5 cubic feet (3 binders)
Correspondence concerning closed banks, 1929-1957, .5 cubic feet
Administrative papers of Liquidation Division, 1935-1960, 2.5 cubic feet
Safe Deposit Box Material, 2 cubic feet
Series 2. Incorporation Files and Special Charters, circa 1913-1957, 4 cubic feet
Series 3. Bank Returns, 1865-1896, 1.5 cubic feet
Series 4. Press Releases, 1997-2011, .25 cubic feet
Series 5. Commissioners Files, 1992-2005, .25 cubic feet
Related Material
None
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. Banking Dept
Subjects:
Banks and banking -- Records and correspondence; Banks and banking -- Connecticut; Banks failures -- Connecticut; Connecticut. Banking Dept -- Records and correspondence
Document Types:
Correspondence; Financial records; Press releases
Restrictions on Access
Safe deposit box material, boxes 96-97 are RESTRICTED.
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Receivership Files, 1918-1971; 92.5 cubic feet
  - Lawsuits against Banks, circa 1930-1939; 2 cubic feet
    - Mechanics Bank (Box 1)
    - Broadway Bank (Box 1)
    - Citizens Bank (Box 1)
    - Hamden Bank (Box 1)
    - West Haven Bank (Box 2)
    - Mechanics Bank, completed (Box 2)
    - Broadway Bank, completed (Box 2)
    - Citizens Bank, completed (Box 2)
    - Hamden Bank, completed (Box 2)
    - West Haven Bank, completed (Box 2)
  - General Correspondence, circa 1920-1969; 6 cubic feet
    - Higganum Savings Bank (Box 3)
    - Home Bank and Trust Company, Darien (Box 3)
    - Home Bank & Trust Company, South Manchester (Box 3)
    - Home Bank & Trust Company, West Haven (Box 3)
    - Home Building and Loan Association, Bridgeport (Box 3)
    - Home Building & Loan Association of Hartford, Inc. (Box 3)
    - Hughes, Arthur M. R. (Box 3)
    - Industrial Bank of Commerce, Middletown (Box 3)
    - Industrial Bank of Hartford, Inc. (Box 3)
    - Investors Mortgage Company, Bridgeport (Box 3)
    - Italia-America Shipping Corporation (Box 3)
    - Jacobs (Ward W.) & Company, Hartford (Box 3)
    - Jefferson Trust Company (Box 3)
    - Kazemekas and Son Inc., Waterbury (Box 3)
    - Kennedy, James H., successors to Walter T. Kenyon, Hamden (Box 3)
    - Killingly Trust Company, Danielson (Box 3)
    - Kinney Realty Company, New Haven (Box 3)
    - Koletar, Joseph, Bridgeport (Box 3)
    - Kusterer Mortgage Corporation, New Haven (Box 3)
    - Lincoln Bank and Trust Company, Stamford (Box 4)
    - Lincoln (Charles T.) Company, New Haven (Box 4)
    - Lomas & Nettleton Mortgage Company, New Haven (Box 4)
    - Lupo, Gabriele, Hamden (Box 4)
    - Lyman, Charles M., New Haven (Box 4)
    - Madison Trust Company, 5 folders (Box 4)
    - Maisano (Donato) & Brother, New Haven (Box 4)
    - Malley (Edward) Company, New Haven, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Manchester Trust Company (Box 4)
    - Mancini Ruggiero and Palomba Company, Waterbury, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Mariners Savings Bank, New London (Box 4)
    - Merchants Bank and Trust Company, Hartford (Box 4)
    - Meriden Industrial Bank, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Middlesex Banking Company (Box 4)
    - Middletown Savings and Loan Association, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Middletown Trust Company (Box 4)
    - Milford Trust Company (Box 4)
    - Mongillo, J., Derby (Box 4)
    - Moosup Trust Company, 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Morris Plan Bank of Bridgeport (Box 5)
    - Morris Plan Bank of Hartford (Box 5)
    - Morris Plan Bank of New Haven, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Morris Plan Bank of Stamford, 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Morris Plan Bank of Waterbury (Box 5)
    - Morton, R. E. (Box 5)
    - Mutual Bank & Trust Company, Hartford (Box 5)
    - Mystic Building and Loan Association (Box 5)
    - Mystic Savings and Loan Association, Stonington, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - National Iron Bank of Falls Village (Box 5)
    - Naugatuck Valley Morris Plan Bank, Ansonia (Box 5)
    - Navigazione Generale Italiana (Box 5)
    - New Britain Co-operative Savings & Loan Association (Box 5)
    - New England Title & Guaranty Company, New Haven (Box 5)
    - Newfield Bank & Trust Company, Bridgeport (Box 5)
    - New Hartford Savings Bank (Box 5)
    - New Hartford Trust Company (Box 5)
    - New Haven Progressive Building and Loan Association (Box 5)
    - New London Morris Plan Company (Box 5)
    - New London Trust & Safe Deposit Company (Box 5)
    - Norfolk Savings Bank (Box 5)
    - North End Bank and Trust Company, Bridgeport, 3 folders (Box 6)
    - North End Building & Loan Association, Bridgeport (Box 6)
    - The North Side Bank and Trust Company, Bristol, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Norwalk Building, Loan and Investment Association, 3 folders (Box 6)
    - Orange Bank & Trust Company, West Haven (Box 6)
    - Pallotti, Andretta & Company, Hartford (Box 6)
    - Pallotti, Andretta & Company, New Haven (Box 6)
    - Park City Savings and Loan Association, Bridgeport, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Park Street Trust Company, Hartford (Box 6)
    - People's Bank & Trust Company, Branford (Box 6)
    - People's Bank & Trust Company, New Haven (Box 6)
    - People's Bank & Trust Company, Waterbury (Box 6)
    - People's Savings Bank, Bridgeport (Box 6)
    - People's Trust Company, South Norwalk (Box 6)
    - Persky, Simon, New Haven (Box 7)
    - Phoenix State Bank and Trust Company, Hartford, 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Podoloff (A.) & Sons, Inc., New Haven (Box 7)
    - Portland Building and Loan Association, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Portland Trust Company (Box 7)
    - Progressive Savings and Loan Association, 4 folders (Box 7)
    - Puritan Bank and Trust Company (Box 7)
    - Puritan Bank and Trust Company, Meriden, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Pyramid Corporation, Stamford (Box 7)
    - Riverside Trust Company, Hartford, 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Robbins Burrall Trust Company, Lakeville (Box 7)
    - Rockville Bank (Box 7)
    - Rockville Building and Loan Association (Box 7)
    - Rocky Hill Bank and Trust Company, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Russo, Paul, New Haven (Box 7)
    - Salem Trust Company, Naugatuck (Box 7)
    - Salisbury, E.E., Moosup (Box 7)
    - Salisbury, Savings Society of, Lakeville (Box 8)
    - Sanditz & Traurig, Waterbury (Box 8)
    - Security Bank & Trust Company, Stamford (Box 8)
    - Security Trust Company, Hartford (Box 8)
    - Shelton trust Company (Box 8)
    - Smith (Elmer E.) Company, New Haven (Box 8)
    - Smith, Edward B. East Norwalk (Box 8)
    - Smith, William B., Bridgeport (Box 8)
    - Sons of Italy Industrial Bank, New Haven (Box 8)
    - South Norwalk Trust Company, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Southport Savings Bank (Box 8)
    - Southport Trust Company (Box 8)
    - Squire (W.H.) Company, Meriden, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Stafford Savings and Loan Association, Inc., 3 folders (Box 8)
    - Stamford Building and Loan Association (Box 8)
    - Stamford Industrial Bank (Box 8)
    - Standard Mortgage Corporation, Bridgeport (Box 8)
    - State Bank & Trust Company, Hartford (Box 8)
    - Stratford Building & Loan Association (Box 8)
  - Complete Bank Files, circa 1930-1959; 4 cubic feet
    - East Hampton Bank and Trust Company (Box 9-10)
    - Hamden Bank and Trust Company (Box 11)
    - Naugatuck Bank and Trust Company (Box 11)
    - Pawcatuck Bank and Trust Company (Box 12)
  - Trust Department, circa 1920-1959; 2 cubic feet
    - Manchester Trust and Safe Deposit Company (Box 13-14)
  - Special Banking Subjects, circa 1940-1959; 7 cubic feet
    - Bank Holidays, Emergency Period, Federal Emergency Bank Bill (Box 15)
    - Bank Failures - Causes - Reorganizations (Box 15)
    - Bank Failures, Investigations of (Box 15)
    - Banking Department Expenditures, Analysis of, for Calendar Year 1926 and Costs of Examining as a Basis for Equitable Distribution of Assessments (Box 15)
    - Banking Department Expenses regarding 1941 New Apportionment Law (Box 15)
    - Bill to Bring F.D.I.C. under Government Controls Act, Section 308 of H.R. 3756 (Box 15)
    - Bretton Woods Agreement (Box 15)
    - Post-War Small Business Credit - Smaller War Plants Corporation (Box 15)
    - Chapter House Circle of the King's Daughters vs. Hartford National Bank and Trust Company (Box 15)
    - Check-Cashing for State Employees (Box 15)
    - Federal Reserve Voluntary Credit Program (Box 15)
    - Management and Labor Problems (Box 15)
    - Pledging of Savings Accounts as Collateral (Box 15)
    - Post-War Planning (Box 15)
    - Regulation "W" (Box 15)
    - Regulation "X" (Box 16)
    - Revaluation of Savings Bank Assets (Box 16)
    - Social Security Act (Box 16)
    - Stamford Trust Company, Western Conn. Title & Mortgage Certificates (Box 16)
    - T.A.D. Jones Mortgage Bond Issue with Foreign Bank As Trustee (Box 16)
    - Audit Bill, 1949 Session, Did not pass (Box 16)
    - Current Hearing File, Commissioner Rapport (Box 16)
    - Bank Holding Company (Box 16)
    - NASSB Commodity Credit Corp. Participation Notes (Box 16)
    - NASSB Coordinating Committee - Absorption of Exchange Charges (Box 16)
    - NASSB Coordinating Committee - Special Subjects (Box 16)
    - NASSB Coordinating Committee - Meeting Arrangement Correspondence (Box 16)
    - NASSB Coordinating Committee - Supervisory Agreement (Box 16)
    - Directors" Meetings Called by Examiners (Box 16)
    - F.D.I.C Controversy (Box 17)
    - Federal Legislation (Box 17)
    - National Association of Supervisors of State Banks, Federal Legislation (Box 17)
    - Legislation - State and Federal (Box 17)
    - NASSB - Federal Legislation, Credit Union Bill - S. 2890 (Box 17)
    - Federal Savings and Loan Branch Bill S. 975, 1954 Material (Box 17)
    - NASSB - Housing Bill (Box 17)
    - Patman Questionnaire (Box 17)
    - Reorganization Plan (Federal) (Box 17)
    - Reserve Requirements and Non-Member Banks (S. 1775) (1949) (Box 17)
    - Savings and Loan Competition and Other Material (National Association of Supervisors of State Banks) (Box 17)
    - National Association of State Bank Supervisors - Savings and Loan Matters (Committee) (Box 17)
    - Statements Before Committees of Congress (Box 17)
    - NASSB - Small Business Administration Participations (Box 17)
    - National Association of Supervisors of State Banks, Committee on Supervisory Matters (Trusts) (Box 17)
    - National Association of Supervisors of State Banks, Committee on Trust Supervisory Matters, Special Topics (Box 17)
    - NASSB - Conference Folder (Box 18)
    - NASSB - District Material, 1953-1954 (Box 18)
    - NASSB - Conference Speakers" Program (Box 18)
    - Special Cases - Kearny Federal Savings and Loan Association, Massachusetts and Florida Controversies, Re: Establishment of Federal Savings and Loan Branches (Box 18)
    - Savings and Loan Branch Matters - Current (Box 18)
    - National Supervisors" Association, Home Loan Board Resolution (Box 18)
    - National Association of Supervisors, (S. 975) Congressional Research (Box 18)
    - National Association of Supervisors of State Banks, Committee on Trust Supervisory Matters, Special Topics (Box 18)
    - National Association of Supervisors of State Banks, Stephenson's Conferences (Box 18)
    - Untitled folder (Box 18)
    - Douglas-Flanders Questionnaire (August - October 1949) (Box 19)
    - Conversion Bill - H.R. 1161 (Box 19)
    - Credit Union Taxation (1947) (Box 19)
    - Appraisal of Assets Agreement (Box 19)
    - Bank Credit Policy During Inflation - Joint Statement With Federal Authorities (Box 19)
    - Bank Holding Company Legislation - 1949 and Prior Thereto (Box 19)
    - Convention Letters and Correspondence (Box 19)
    - Form Letters From Officers and Committees (Box 19)
    - Aba Model Code (Box 19)
    - Tentative Draft Model State Banking Code (Box 19)
    - Alker Bill Re: Defenses to FDIC Collecting, (H.R. 5811) 1949 (Box 19)
    - Perpetual Inventory File (Box 20)
    - Association Exam As of (Box 20)
    - Home Loan Bank Board Matters, Annual Report and Examination Forms (Box 20)
    - National Association of State Savings, Building & Loan Supervisors, Uniform and Monthly Reports (Box 20)
    - Uniform Bank Examinations (Box 20)
    - Earnings Report Forms and Phraseology (Box 20)
    - National Association, Washington Hotel Material - Not Mayflower (Box 20)
    - National Association of Supervisors of State Banks, National Board of Bank Examiners (Vardaman) (Box 20)
    - Regulation U - 1940 (Box 20)
    - Uniform Savings Report Form Material, N.A.S.S.B. (Box 20)
    - FDIC Revision Bill (S. 2822) (January 1950) (Box 20)
    - FDIC Rules and Regulations (1946-1947) (Box 20)
    - International Bank For Reconstruction and Development (1947) (Box 20)
    - Savings and Loan Conference - Bridgeport - November 16-18, 1952 (Box 20)
    - National Association B/L Supervisors - Relations With Federal Authority Committee (Box 20)
    - National Association B/L Supervisors - District Meetings (Box 20)
    - Conversion Bills, National Association of State Savings & Building & Loan Association (Box 20)
    - National Association of State Savings, Building and Loan Supervisors (Box 20)
    - National Association of State Savings, Building and Loan Supervisors, Current (Box 20)
    - Wagner Questionnaire (Box 20)
    - Conversion of Federal Savings and Loan Association to Mutual Savings Banks (Box 21)
    - Federal Savings Bank Plan (Box 21)
    - Legislative File - National Association of State Savings, Building and Loan Supervisors (Box 21)
    - Regulations, Savings and Loan - By Home Loan Bank Board (Box 21)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission Bill, S. 2408, National Association of State Savings, Building and Loan Supervisors (Box 21)
    - Savings and Loan Branch Bill (Box 21)
      - Resolutions, Duplicate Letters, Etc. (Box 21)
      - Newspaper Articles (Box 21)
      - The Bill Letters to Congressmen, Etc. (Box 21)
    - Extra Copies - Branch Savings and Loan Bills - Originals and Copies (Box 21)
    - Savings and Loan Branches, National Association of State Savings & Building & Loan Association (Box 21)
    - Resolutions Re: Branches, Liquidity, Etc. (Box 21)
    - Savings and Loan Branch Materials and Specific Federal Applications (Box 21)
    - Federal Savings and Loan Advisory Council (Box 21)
    - Advisory Council - December 13-14, 1951 Meeting (Box 21)
    - Advisory Council - May 7-8, 1951 Meeting (Box 21)
    - National Association of Supervisors of State Banks, Special Committee on Trust Supervision (Box 21)
    - Trust Supervision By State Banking Departments (Box 21)
  - By-Laws of Savings Banks, circa 1930-1949; 2 cubic feet
    - 1941 Bills Heard (Legislative) (Box 22)
    - Bills Heard by Banking Committee, 1939 (Box 22)
    - 1941 Legislative File (Box 22)
    - Savings Bank Life Insurance - 1937 (Legislative File) (Box 22)
    - 1939 Legislative (Box 22)
      - Legislative Correspondence (1939-1944) (Box 22)
      - 1939 Legislative (Box 22)
    - Obsolete By-Laws of Savings Banks, 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - 1943 Legislative File (Box 23)
    - Legislative Council, 1943 (Box 23)
    - 1943 Bills Heard (with memos) (Box 23)
    - House Bills Rejected (1945) (Box 23)
    - 1945 Legislative - H.M.E. (Box 23)
    - House Bills Passed (1945) (Box 23)
    - Senate Bills (1945) (Box 23)
      - Passed (Box 23)
      - Rejected (Box 23)
    - Bills Passed in Special Session, May 7th to 16th, 1946 (Box 23)
    - Bills Not Passed, 1947 Session (Box 23)
    - Code Bills Passed, 1947 Session (Box 23)
  - Legislation, circa 1940-1971; 12 cubic feet
    - 1959 Legislative File (Box 24)
    - Legislative Material Re: H.B. 2070 - An Act Concerning The Uniform Commercial Code (1959 Session of the G.A.) (Box 24)
    - Building and Loan Legislation (Box 24)
    - Connecticut Securities Act, 1959 Legislation (Box 24)
    - Credit Union Legislation (Box 24)
    - Industrial Banks, 1959 Legislation (Box 24)
    - Money Forwarders, 1959 Legislation (Box 24)
    - Private Bankers, 1959 Legislation (Box 24)
    - Sales Finance Companies, 1959 Legislation (Box 24)
    - Savings Bank Legislation and/or Savings Depts. (Box 24)
    - 1959 Small Loan Legislation (Box 24)
    - State Banks & Trust Companies, 1959 Legislation (Box 24)
    - Personnel, 1959 Legislation (Re: Al De Roehn) (Box 24)
    - Laws of General Interest, 1959 Legislation (Box 24)
    - 1959 - Final Legislative Record Index (Box 24)
    - 1959 Report of the Legislative Council (Box 24)
    - 1959 Legislative Record Pertaining to Banks and Other Related Institutions (Box 24)
    - Senate and House Bills Not Passed, 1949 Legislature (Box 24A)
    - 1949 Legislation Pertaining to Banking (Box 24A)
    - Senate Bills Passed, 1949 Legislature (Box 24A)
    - House Bills Passed, 1949 Legislature (Box 24A)
    - 1951 Banking Department Memo (Box 24A)
    - 1951 Legislation Pertaining to Banking and Related Matters (Box 24A)
    - House Bills Passed, 1951 Legislature (Box 24A)
    - Senate Bills Passed, 1951 Legislature (Box 24A)
    - 1953 Legislature - House and Senate Bills Passed (Box 24A)
    - Senate and House Bills Not Passed, 1951 Legislature (Box 24A)
    - 1953 Legislative Record Pertaining to Banking and other Related Bills (Box 24A)
    - Senate and House Bills Not Passed, 1953 Legislature (Box 24A)
      - 1953 Banking Department Memoranda, Miscellaneous Correspondence, Summaries, Etc. (Box 24A)
    - Extra Copies of Bills Presented at March, 1958, Special Session (Box 25)
    - Extra Copies of Engrossed Bills and Legislative Record Index (Final Edition) (Box 25)
    - Uniform Commercial Code - H.B. 71-HJR 86 (1953 Session) - and HJR 90 (1955 Session) (Box 25)
    - House and Senate Bills Passed at the March, 1958, Special Session (Box 25)
    - Extra Copies of Charter Revisions (Box 25)
    - House and Senate Bills Not Passed at the March, 1958, Special Session (Box 25)
    - 1957 Report of the Legislative Council (Box 25)
    - Legislation Presented at September 1957 Session of the Legislature (Box 25)
    - Special Acts, 1949-1951-1953-1955 (Box 25)
    - 1957 Legislative Record Pertaining to Banks and Other Related Institutions (Box 25)
    - 1957 Legislative Correspondence, Re: Various Bills (Box 25)
    - House and Senate Bills Not Passed - 1957 Legislature (Box 25)
    - House and Senate Bills Approved - 1957 Session of Legislature (Box 25)
    - Proposed Recodification and Revision of the Connecticut Banking Law (Box 26)
    - Mortgage Lending Statute Proposal, Re: House Bills 1258 and 1544, 1955, General Assembly Referred to Legislative Council (Box 26)
    - Senate and House Bills Not Passed, 1955 Legislature (Box 26)
    - House and Senate Bills Presented at November Special Session of the Legislature (1955) (Box 26)
    - Savings Bank Legislation, 1955 (Box 26)
    - 1955, November Special Session (Box 26)
    - 1955, Banking Department Memoranda on Bills Presented (Box 26)
    - 1955 Legislative Record Pertaining to Banking and Other Related Bills (Box 26)
    - 1955, Miscellaneous Legislation Sponsored By - Connecticut Bankers Association, Savings Banks" Association of Connecticut, Savings & Loan League of Connecticut, Counsel for Industrial Bank Group, Connecticut Credit Union League (Box 26)
    - House and Senate Bills Approved, 1955 Session (Box 26)
    - Burritt Mutual Savings Bank, Trusteed Pension Plan (Box 27)
    - Connecticut Savings Banks, Miscellaneous Material (Box 27)
    - Canaan Savings Bank (Box 27)
    - Chelsea Savings Bank, Norwich (Box 27)
    - Citizens Savings Bank, Stamford (Box 27)
    - Derby Savings Bank, Trusteed Pension Plan (Box 27)
    - Dime Savings Bank, Wallingford, Pension Plan (Box 27)
    - Essex Savings Bank, Trusteed Pension Plan (Box 27)
    - Falls Village Savings Bank, Employees" Pension Trust (Box 27)
    - Groton Savings Bank, Mystic (Box 27)
    - Mechanics and Farmers Savings Bank, Bridgeport (Box 27)
    - Meriden Savings Bank (Box 27)
    - Middletown Savings Bank (Box 27)
    - Moodus Savings Bank (Box 27)
    - National Savings Bank, New Haven (Box 27)
    - Newtown Savings Bank (Box 27)
    - New Milford Savings Bank, Pension Plan (Box 27)
    - Norwalk Savings Society (Box 27)
    - Norwich Savings Society (Box 27)
    - People's Savings Bank, New Britain, Pension Plan (Box 27)
    - Suffield Savings Bank (Box 27)
    - Savings Bank Life Insurance Fund, Inc. (Box 27)
    - Savings Banks" Association of Connecticut (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous Legislation, Bills Not Passed (Box 28)
    - Senate Bills (Box 28)
      - Legislative Memorandums (Box 28)
    - Banking Department Assessment and Fee Plan Sheets for Income, Expense (Box 28)
    - Savings Banks, Bills Not Passed (Box 28)